Subtitles by Salrith
[Door closes]
I have to finish all this
...going to steam the tablecloth for tonight
I'm going to paint over that...
Water stain in the ceiling
Like this afternoon?
Evelyn: Five minutes!
Waymond: What?
Waymond: Okay--
Evelyn: Which paint did you use?
Joy's here!
Go set the table, he must be hungry!
Waymond: Can we talk later?
[Door slams]
[Sighs]
Joy: Hey, hey!
Joy: Hey!
Thank you for doing this.
Joy: You look really pretty right now.
Becky: Oh!
You like this...
...this hot Mormon look?
Joy: I'm just telling you now in case my mom says something dumb like you're...
...fat, or whatever.
Becky: I thought you said when she says shit like that it means she cares?
Hi, Evelyn!
Mrs Wong!
Joy: Hey, mom.
I only cook enough food for three people
Now I have to cook more.
It's Joy.
She brought Becky!
Joy: Hiiiii
Waymond: Hi, honey!
Becky: Hi, Mr. Wong!
Waymond: Hi, Becky!
Thank you for coming!
Please, call me Waymond!
Evelyn: You know...
He doesn't have to stay.
Joy: Who's 'he'?
Evelyn: Becky!
Joy: Becky's a 'she'.
Evelyn: You know me!
I always mix up 'he', 'she'.
In Chinese? Just one word!
'Ta'! So easy.
And the way you two are dressed?
I'm sure I'm not the only one calling him 'he'.
...I mean her 'him'.
Anyways!
My English is f-fine.
And we have Google!
So you don't have to come and be a translator.
Huh?
You stay here, and she can go get-
Joy: Look, I honestly think it's weird okay
Now Becky wants to help
Right, Becky?
Becky: I always learn something when I hang out with the elderly
Old people are very wise.
Evelyn: Hmm.
Evelyn: It's okay.
We'll take Gong-gong with us to the meeting.
Uh, you and Becky can stay here and decorate.
Becky: Where is he? When can I meet him?
Joy: [Clears throat]
[Doorbell buzz]
Evelyn: Customers!
Eat. Fast!
Joy: Mom.
Evelyn: What?
Joy: Mom, just wait.
Evelyn: Wait? Wait, no time to wait today.
Joy: Just, please
Evelyn: Joy-a, any other time I beg you to come and eat.
Or call me or anything
but today very busy.
Joy: Mom, this is literally what it's always like.
Evelyn: Wrong white paint!
Joy: Look, I know you haven't always liked Becky, okay
Evelyn: I like Becky! She is very nice!
You are very lucky--
Joy: ...She's half Mexican...
Evelyn: No shoes in washer!
Broken? You pay-uh.
But Gong-gong?
His heart cannot take it!
Especially after such a long flight!
You want him to come all the way from China to die like that?
He's not gonna die!
Big-nose: That's not what I said. What I said--
Big-nose: Just hold on. I can't hear you! Just hold on.
Evelyn: How can I help you?
Big-nose: Yeah I'm here to pick up some shirts
I called like three times.
Evelyn: Okay. Give me your ticket. I find for you.
Big-nose: No, I have the ticket!
She's just asking for it, that's like the way that it works.
They don't read minds.
Then-then hang up!
Thank you.
Joy: We've been together for three years.
Don't you think Gong-gong would want to know?
Evelyn: Let him enjoy his party tonight!
Joy: You think Becky is gonna get through the whole
party without introducing herself--
Man: Evelyyyyn.
Joy: You think Becky is gonna get through the whole
party without introducing herself--
Guess whose $20 got eaten by the machine again.
Waymond! Customers need you!
Waymond (muffled): Alright, coming!
Man: Evelyn!
You know my wife used to wear that exact same
perfume, god rest her soul?
Evelyn: Are you coming to the party tonight?
Man: Yeah! Got my ticket right here.
Sorry! It was too crowded here so I moved
some upstairs.
I think the clothes are happier there!
Waymond: See? They're happier here!
NO MORE GOOGLE EYES!
Joy: Mom, can we please talk about Becky?
Evelyn: I still don't know what his brain is thinking.
Joy: Can Becky come tonight, or not?
Evelyn: Stop changing the subject!
Joy: I'm not--
Evelyn: You know he's like our auditor.
She is a terrible person!
She keeps targetting the Chinese in the community.
You know two years of waiting?
She puts a lien on our laundromat.
And you know what your father does?
He brings her cookies.
Every day, I fight, I fight, I fight for all of us.
Every day is a battle here!
Your father! He doesn't care about [inaudible]
I try to make our lives easier and more simple.
Waymond: Evelyn! You have to see Rick dance!
Look, he knows all of the moves!
Waymond: You know Rick is in community theatre?
He wants to be an actor, just like you did!
Waymond: Aah, I love this, hahaha!
Joy: I know! I just- I just- I just
I don't know how to be any fucking clearer!
It's like, she can choose!
Either you come to the party with me
And Gong-gong is eternally shamed until
he forgets it all
And then he dies
Or you don't come with me, and then he still dies!
What??
Evelyn: What are you saying?
Joy: That was a joke.
Waymond: That's not a very funny joke, honey!
Becky: Hey guys...
Man: This is only $10.
I thought you people were very good with math.
Evelyn: Next time I'll give you back
Waymond: Evelyn!
Evelyn: --with interest
Joy: Mom. Mom! MOM!
Waymond: Evelyn!
Evelyn: --with interest
Joy: MOM!
Evelyn: WHAT?!
...Shit, how do you say it?
Uh...
Mom...
Becky: It was nice to meet you!
Evelyn: Also!
There is a Chinese new year party tonight!
Open to all the customers in the community!
Big-nose: Thank you. This is fine.
Evelyn: Please come and enjoy the good food
Evelyn: and nice music, okay?
Big-nose: Alright.
Evelyn: I get you an in- an invite
Moment- moment, please!
Joy!
Wait!
Please!
I have something to say to you!
Joy: What?
You...
...you have to try and eat healthier.
You are getting fat.
[Car door shuts]
[Engine starts]
Waymond: Evelyn?
Evelyn?
[bwah]
Evelyn: Go, go, go, go, go!
Okay!
Evelyn: If I have to think of one more thing
today, my head will explode.
Waymond: You may be in grave danger.
There's no time to explain.
Hold this!
Evelyn: Why are you doing this--
Waymond: Pay attention.
Waymond: When we leave this elevator
you can either turn left towards your scheduled
audit appointment OR
you can turn right and go into the janitors' closet.
Evelyn: Why would I go into the janitors'--
Waymond: Not now.
Evelyn: Ai, oh! Why you download all these
apps on my phone?
Waymond: Breathe in. You're gonna
feel a slight pressure in your head.
Evelyn: Hey, baby Joy!
Evelyn: You come back here!
Joy: Shut. Up.
Evelyn: You don't talk to your mother like this!
Waymond: The moment you're situated
in your meeting
follow these instructions.
But remember.
No one can know.
Don't even talk to me about this because I
won't remember.
Evelyn: But I- I don't-
Waymond: Shh.
Device: Mental scan complete
Waymond: Talk to you soon.
Mrs. Wang.
Auditor: Mrs. Wang, are you with us?
Yes.
Of course.
I'm here!
Just thinking.
Oh, okay. Well,
I was just hoping
that you could explain this.
Evelyn: This is a receipt.
My receipt.
Auditor: I-- look.
I was just hoping you could enlighten me.
As to how, as a laundromat owner
a karaoke machine
could constitute a business expense.
Evelyn: I am a...
singer.
[sighs]
Auditor: Of course you are.
Waymond: It's true!
She has a beautiful voice!
Evelyn! Sing a song for her!
Auditor: No, no! Please, that will
not be necessary, but
I will need a separate Schedule C
for each
of these businesses because
based on what you're trying to deduct
you're also a
novellist
and a chef
Evelyn: Last time you told me
Auditor: No, that-- p-- please.
a teacher
uh
and
a singing coach, an
a watsu technician
I'm sorry
what
what is watsu
Waymond: It's a water massage
(muffled) For back pain, you go get water massage
[beep]
What's happening?
Auditor: --like I'm talking to my ex husband.
Like I said to you before--
It's you messing with my head!
Waymond: Shh!
Evelyn: Don't shh me!
Waymond: Try and match your body.
Evelyn: [muffled screaming]
Waymond: Calm down, please!
Calm down!
Relax your body in the other universe.
Please.
Waymond: Go into autopilot.
Good... Good.
They don't know you and I
are in this universe yet.
So hopefully, I'll have some time
to explain.
I'm not your husband
at least, not the one you know
I'm another version of him
from another life path
- another universe
I'm here because we need your help!
Evelyn: Very busy today!
No time to help you!
Waymond: There's a great evil
that has taken root in my world
and it's begun spreading its chaos
throughout the many verses
I've spent years
searching for the one
who might be the match
to this great evil
with an even greater good
and bring back balance!
All those years of searching
have brought me here.
(muffled) Mrs. Wang?
To this universe.
To you.
(Muffled) Hello?
I know it's a lot to take in right now
Auditor: Mrs. Wang?
MRS. WANG.
Hellooo?
Look, I-
I'm sure you have a lot on your mind
But I-
cannot imagine anything mattering more
than the
conversation we are now having
concerning your tax liability.
I-
need I remind you
that there's already a lien on your property
Repossession is well within our rights
Evelyn: I know.
I am paying attention.
Auditor: Do you see these?
You don't get one of these
unless you've seen a lot of bullshit.
Excuse my French
Now you may
only see a pile of boring forms and numbers
but I see a story
With nothing
but a stack of receipts
I can trace the ups and downs of your life
And it does not look good.
It does not
look
good.
Waymond: Sorry.
My wife confuses her hobbies for businesses.
An honest mistake!
Auditor: ...Okay.
Well.
With all of these, um...
"Honest mistakes", I mean
even if we don't charge you with
fraud, we'll
most certainly have to fine you for
gross neglicence.
Evelyn: You always trying to confuse us with these...
big words.
Auditor: I. Thought. You. Were.
Going. To. Bring. Your. Daughter
to help
you translate.
Evelyn: I AM going to bring my-
Sorry
Evelyn
Waymond: Evelyn!
Are you paying attention?
Evelyn: I cannot talk now!
Unless you can help me with my taxes?
What is "gross necklaces?"
Waymond: I know you have a lot
of things on your mind.
But nothing could possibly matter more
than this conversation we're having
right now
concerning the fate of every single world
of our infinite multiverse
(muffled) No respect for my...
Waymond: My dear Evelyn...
I know you.
With every passing moment you fear
you might have missed your chance
to make something of your life
I'm here to tell you
Every rejection
Every disappointment
has led you here
to this moment
don't let anything distract you from it
Auditor: Do you think
this is funny?
Waymond: So what will it be?
Our time here is up!
They're gonna kill us.
Evelyn: What?
Waymond: Do you think you can give
us more time so we can redo all this?
Do not worry
This is just a votive universe
we were using for communication
You will know when it is time to fight.
Auditor: You wanna redo...
You're gonna resubmit?
Waymond: I will be in contact soon.
Evelyn: I think my other half is
messing up the audit-
Waymond: Maybe we, uh-
we can look at all the receipts again?
Evelyn!
Trust no one!
[screams]
Oh, no no no no no no-
Auditor: Oh dear lord.
Everything... okay.
I think I forget something at home.
Auditor: Uh.
Siddown.
Think I'm gonna regret this...
You can go.
What?
You-
You will have-
You will have until I leave the office
tonight
to bring everything in.
Six PM.
Last chance.
Oh
Tomorrow is better--
Waymond: Thank you!
Thank you! Six PM.
Thank you so much.
Auditor: Thank you for the cookies.
They look delicious.
Last chance!
Waymond: Have a nice day!
(Echoing) Last chance!
Waymond: Evelyn!
Evelyn!
So you know about this?
It was you. Like, you!
Who was in the elevator!
I was in the elevator
Evelyn: Come back next week.
[Glares in auditor]
(whispers) I'm not ready to fight!
I am not ready to fight!
Waymond: Maybe we don't have a choice
Waymond: Switch shoes to- whaA!
Auditor: Wha-OH!
Auditor: Someone call security!
Waymond: What are you doing?!
Evelyn: YOU! Told me to do it!
You said I would know when
it is the time to fight!
She was coming after us!
Auditor: Oh, you have
NO idea, lady
Assaulting an IRS agent?!
You have NO idea
"Dissolution of Marriage"?
Auditor: Yes, at the moment
Your brother gets a divorce
Now you think divorce is ok?
Waymond: I don't think it's ok!
Evelyn: We made a sacred promise!
Other Waymond: I told you to stay low
and out of sight.
Oh.
NOW you are here!
Evelyn: Stop confusing me,
coming and going
Stop it! Stop it!
Waymond: Relax
I'll get you out of this.
Evelyn: Stop coming here!
Guard: Okay, folks.
Everyone remain calm
Auditor: Oh, thank
Auditor: Thank god, it's-
Auditor: that one right there,
the Chinese lady
Evelyn: No!
It's all his fault!
Guard: Okay, I need you two
to get on the ground with your hands
behind your head
Evelyn: Ok
Guard: Sir, please comply.
Guard: Okay, whatever you're
thinking about doing
don't do it
[delicious chapstick smack]
Guard: ...Sir?
[beep]
It's okay.
[spicy wink]
Guard: Okay sir, that's enough
Evelyn: Oh shit
[slowmo no]
[Fuck of realization]
Waymond: On your feet
Evelyn: Who...
What is happening?
Waymond: I'm not the Waymond who
wants to divorce you
I'm the Waymond who's
saving your life
Now, you can either come
with me and live up to your
ultimate potential
Or lie here and live
with the consequences
Evelyn: I want to lie here.
Evelyn: Aah!
Evelyn: Hey-
Evelyn: no put me down!
Auditor: Citizens...
of the four thousand
six hundred
and fifty-fifth flavour-verse
you are about
to be graced
by the presence
of our sovereign leader
Jobu Tupaki!
Now, let me assure you of something
Just like the rest of your
miserable lives, this is
nothing more
than a statistical inevitability
Jobu Tupaki: Duck
Auditor: Jobu Tupaki has seen
all and knows all
She knows
what makes you tick
what fragile branches
your self worth rests
Jobu Tupaki: Goose
Evelyn: [Gasps]
[Screams in multiverse]
[Explosion]
Jobu Tupaki: Hang on
Jobu Tupaki: Don't die yet, alright?
Jobu Tupaki: Buddy?
Jobu Tupaki: [Sighs]
Jobu Tupaki: Shhhhh!
Jobu Tupaki: It's not her.
Jobu Tupaki: They might be close.
[Channel switching]
Becky: Is that where
your parents are?
Are you ok?
Hey!
Joy?
Evelyn: My husband won't even kill
a spider
How can you be the
same person?
Waymond: You underestimate how
the smallest decisions can compound
to significant differences over a lifetime
Every tiny decision creates
another branching universe. And if-
Were you not paying
attention before?
Evelyn: Of course!
You're just very bad
at explain--
Waymond: Shh!
Evelyn: Don't push me!
Evelyn: Oh my god!
We have to go back!
We forgot my father!
Waymond: Don't worry
We're monitoring him
He's safe
Evelyn: No, no - are you sure?
Waymond: Yes!
Look, this is your universe
One bubble floating in
a cosmic foam of existence
Every surrounding bubble
has slight variations
but the further away you
get from your universe
the bigger the differences.
This is where I am from
The Alpha Verse
The first universe to
make contact with the others
You can call me
Alpha Waymond
In this world
You
were a brilliant woman.
In your search to prove the existence
of other universes
You discovered a way
to temporarily link
your consciousness
to another version of yourself
accessing alternate memories
their skills
even their emotions
Evelyn: Like... you
with the
fanny pack?
Alpha Waymond: Exactly
It's called Verse Jumping
and I need you to
learn how to do it
Right now
Evelyn: Right now?!
Alpha Waymond: It may be our
only chance of getting out of here alive!
[beep]
Two guards coming this way
On my signal, try to blend in
Why don't you get YOU
Evelyn to do this?
Alpha Waymond:
My Evelyn is dead.
Go!
Alpha Waymond:
OH MY GOD!
WHAT'S GOING ON?!
Help us!
Evelyn: How did I die?
Alpha Waymond:
I've seen you die a thousand ways
In a thousand worlds
In every single one
you were murdered.
Evelyn: What?!
Why would anybody
want to kill me?!
Alpha Waymond:
She's an omniversal being
with unimaginable power
an agent of pure chaos
with no real motives or desires
Jobu Tupaki
Evelyn: You're just
making up sounds!
We need another exit.
Evelyn: So let her
destroy the other bubbles.
You said there are so many of them!
Maybe it's okay if
we lose some
but just
leave me out of it
Alpha Waymond:
It's not so simple.
She's been building something.
We thought it was some
sort of black hole
But it appears to
consume more than just
light and matter
We don't know exactly
what it is
We don't know what it's for
But we can all...
feel it
You've been feeling it, too
haven't you?
Something is off
Your clothes never wear as
well the next day
Your hair never falls
in quite the same way
Even your coffee tastes...
wrong.
Our institutions are crumbling
Nobody...
trusts their neighbour anymore
And you stay up at night
wondering to yourself
Evelyn: How can we get back?
Alpha Waymond:
This
is the Alpha Verse mission
To take us back to
how it's supposed to be
But that begins with
finding the one
who can stand up to Jobu's
perverse shard of chaos
Evelyn: And you think
it's me?
Alpha Waymond:
Why else would we risk everything
to get you out of here?
Oh...
There you are.
Oh!
Evelyn: Ms. Dierdre!
I'm-
sorry I punched you, but-
Look
I think I finally understand
why-
[gasps]
What is she doing?!
Alpha Waymond:
Verse jumping. Run!
[beep]
[screams in IRS]
She jumped somewhere. Brute force.
Sumo wrestler? Body builder?
Doesn't matter.
Counter with someone agile!
On your perimeter we've got
a break dancer
mime
gymnast
Give me gymnast. Go!
Calculating route...
Okay, so papercuts.
Four of them!
One between each finger.
Papercuts won't
happen when you- I'm trying!
It's impossible
Probability one in eight thousand
It's the strongest
jumping path we have.
What you doing?
There we go. One!
There's two
Three!
A'ight come on come on come on
Stay with me
FOUR! There it is!
Okay c'mon, jump!
Is that... pro wrestling?
She's going for
a back breaker!
She's gotta run
No! She can jump
Somewhere, she can fight
She's not ready
A jump like that would
fry most people
She's not most people.
Damn!
What a weak body
Hello?
Alpha Waymond:
Evelyn
Can you hear me?
You're gonna have to
verse jump
Verse jump?!
Hello?
Concentrate on a universe
in which you
studied martial arts
Okay, I'm locking in
Calculations complete.
Profess your love.
Alpha Waymond:
You're gonna have to profess
your love to Dierdre
No way!
Alpha Waymond:
It's your jumping path!
It's like eating the chapstick
or switching shoes
We developed an algorithm
that calculates which statistically
improbable action will place you
in the universe on the edge
of your local cluster
which then slingshots you
to the desired universe
Evelyn: Stupid!
Doesn't make any sense!
Alpha Waymond:
Exactly!
The less sense it makes
the better
The stochastic pass algorithm's
fuelled by random actions
Tell her you love her
and mean it!
Are there any other jumping paths?
The next best paths are
break your own arm
or take a nap
You're not sleepy, are you?
I love you?
Jumping path failure.
Evelyn- wait- no!
[beep]
No!
She's in a level divergent universe
No, no, no!
She's gone home
...to finish her taxes.
This doesn't make any sense...
Think about it
You always get pulled away
Waymond!
I'm sorry, Evelyn
I need to go.
What?
I need to find the right Evelyn.
And this one...
It's not the one.
No!
Wait!
Let me try again!
Alpha Waymond...?
Normal Waymond: Evelyn?!
Waymond: AAA!
What's happened to my hand?!
Go, go, go go!
Evelyn, your face!
Evelyn: You just left me...
You just left me!
Waymond...
Waymond: Ms. Dierdre??
Evelyn: I love you!
I love you!
[auditor screech]
[choral chanting]
I love you, I love you...
I...
love...
you...
[successful beep]
I...
Love...
Evelyn?
Evelyn: Oh, I'm so happy
to be here today
Evelyn?
Evelyn?!
Why did you-
How-
It was beautiful!
Waymond...
Alpha Waymond:
We better keep moving.
Now you've definitely
got Jobu's attention
Come on!
Stay calm!
Your brain is under an
incredible amount of stress
Evelyn: Let me finish talking with my husband
He needs to know
how good my life could have been
Are you with me?
Evelyn: I thought I was disconnected?
Why was I still there?
Alpha Waymond:
Your mind
is like a clay pot holding water
every jump opens another crack
causing things to leak through
With training
you will learn to reseal these cracks
Eat.
You need energy.
Cream cheese...
Mmm!
In my universe
the cattle were killed off
one of the many things we lost
in our war against Jobu
Evelyn: What if...
What if I wanna go back?
What if I wanna go back
to the other universe?
Alpha Waymond:
SHUT IT DOWN!
Shut it down, you hear me?!
Come back!
Evelyn: Okay, okay, okay!
I'm b- I'm back!
Alpha Waymond:
Listen.
You are only using the other worlds to
acquire special skills, you understand?
If you fall for the temptations,
you invite contradictions
Chaos!
The clay pot could shatter
and you could die
Or far worse...
Evelyn: What can be
worse than death?
We should get moving until we can-
Evelyn: No, no, no!
Enough of your
clay pots
cream cheese, no cows
Explain it all to me.
Now!
Alpha Waymond:
You're right.
In the Alpha Verse...
we began training many young minds
to verse jump
but there was one who was
far and above the most gifted
Our little explorer.
You saw her potential
so you pushed her.
Beyond her limit.
Warning! Unstable!
[beep]
Though overloaded mind usually dies
instead...
her mind was fractured
Warning! Unstable!
Mind fracturing...
Now?
Her mind experiences every world...
...every possibility...
...at the same exact time...
...commanding the infinite knowledge and power
...of the multiverse.
Now she's seen too much
Lost any sense of morality
Any belief in objective truth
Evelyn: What does she want?
Alpha Waymond:
No one knows.
All we know
is she's looking for you.
Hey
You said I was the wrong one
Alpha Waymond:
What you did back there
It changed my mind
You...
were incredible.
Evelyn: Waymond...
Of course.
Evelyn! Come back!
Evelyn!
Jump to another combat universe!
Try peeing yourself, it's
always a good jumping pattern!
C'mon, wake up!
Wake up!
Dierdre: What did you do to me?
Did you staple something to my forehead?!
Evelyn: I didn't do anything!
Guard: We got movement on the elevator
Evelyn: You did it yourself!
Guard: Did we call for backup?
Dierdre: I did not do this to myself!
Police: We detained the assailants
No backup was requested.
You guys are wasting a trip up. Copy?
Alpha Waymond:
Oh no...
She found us.
Police: I said, do you copy?
Clear 'em.
Evelyn: Joy?
Why do you look so stupid?
Police: Ma'am.
You and...
...your pig...
...can't be here.
Is it that I can't
be here?
...Or that I'm not allowed
to be here?
Police: Okay.
Hands where I can see 'em.
Jobu Tupaki: See I can
physically be here.
But what you meant to say
is you're not
allowing me
to be here.
[Both laugh]
Police: Hands behind your back, come on.
Waymond!
Jobu (tearing up):
You gonna make me walk through you?
Police: Yeah, sure kid
I can't let you do that either
Jobu: Again with the CAN'T!
See, I don't think you understand
the meaning of that word
See I can walk through you.
Police: Officer down!
Evelyn: No, no, don't shoot!
Police: Hands on your head!
Jobu: Like this?
Daddyyyy!
[screams]
Don't...
...worry...
...Evelyn...
...it's...
...organic.
[Jobu laughs]
Evelyn: Oh my god...
You...
You're Juju Tubooty?
[spicy wink]
The great evil Waymond
was talking about is...
...my Joy?
Alpha Waymond:
Don't engage!
She can't be reasoned with!
Oh...
It's you
You're the reason
my daughter doesn't call any more!
Why she dropped out of college!
And gets tattoos...
Jobu: Awww.
Evelyn: You...
Why she thinks she is...
(whispers) gay!
[gasp]
[Music stops]
Jobu: I'm so sorry
You're still hung up on
the fact
that I like girls
in this world?
The universe
is so much bigger than you realise
Okay!
No
no
Stop!
Don't make me fight you
I'm...
really good!
Jobu: I don't believe you.
Nice.
You peed yourself.
Alpha Waymond:
No, Evelyn!
You're not locked in!
[beep]
Where did she jump?
She's off the damn map!
(music) Slap your hands...
My hands...
She appears to be in a universe
where everyone has...
Hot dogs instead of fingers
Hot-dog Dierdre:
I mean it just doesn't matter how many times I see it, I'm just so...
[Screams]
An evolutionary branch in the
anatomy of the human race?
A jump like that would fry most people!
Alpha Waymond:
Like I said...
She's not most people.
Hot-dog Dierdre:
Don't!
Why are you treating me like this?
One minute you're so warm
And one minute you're cold
This is crazy!
Jobu: You're starting to get it.
Where you gonna go?
[condiments intensify]
Of all the Evelyns I've seen...
...you're definitely one of
the more interesting ones.
Evelyn: What do you want from me?
Jobu: Here.
Let me help you open up your mind, huh?
Hmm?
Open up.
It's okay.
Take a peek.
Oh, shit...
Evelyn: What is that?
Jobu: I got bored one day.
And I put everything on a bagel.
Everything.
All my hopes and dreams
my...
old report cards
every breed of dog
every last personal ad on Craigslist
Sesame
Poppyseed
Salt.
And it collapsed in on itself
'Cause you see when you really put everything
on a bagel?
It becomes this.
Alpha Waymond:
Come on... Run, Evelyn!
Jobu Tupaki:
The truth...
Evelyn: What...
is the truth?
Jobu Tupaki:
Nothing...
matters.
Evelyn: No, Joy
You don't believe that
Jobu: Feels nice, doesn't it?
If nothing matters...
then all the
pain and guilt you feel for
making nothing of your life
goes away.
(singing) Sucked
intooooo
a bagel...
[looney tunes whump]
Evelyn: Appa?
Gong-gong: Ha! I am not your father.
At least, not the one you know.
I am Alpha Gong-gong!
Evelyn: Not you, too!
Alpha Waymond:
Sir!
What are you doing here?
Alpha Gong-gong:
We need to go!
Just follow me.
Alpha Waymond:
Sir, I have this under control
Alpha Gong-gong:
Again, you deliberately disobey me
And caused another mind to be...
Compromised
[ominous wheelchair creaking]
And now...
You know what we must do.
Alpha Waymond:
No!
Please!
She's unlike anything we've seen!
She could finally stop Jobu Tupaki!
Evelyn: You mean the monster
that is inside my daughter?
Why didn't you tell me about it earlier?!
What else are you Alpha people
not telling me?
Did you see her dance that man to death?
There is no way
I am the Evelyn you are looking for
Alpha Waymond:
No.
I see you so clearly.
Evelyn: See what?
I'm...
no good at anything.
Alpha Waymond:
Exactly!
I've seen thousands of Evelyns
but never
an Evelyn like you
You have so many goals you never finished
Dreams
you never followed
You're living
your worst you
Evelyn: I cannot be the worst
What about that hot-dog one?
Alpha Waymond:
No.
Can't you see?
Every failure here
branched off into a success
for another Evelyn
in another life
most people
only have a few significant alternate
life paths so close to them
But you?
Here?
You're capable of anything
because you're so bad
at everything
Alpha Gong-gong:
What good is all that power
when her mind is already succumbing to that
chaos, huh?
[knocking in Jobu]
Hello?
Hello, mom, dad, what's--
[knocking in Jobu]
No
Do not answer her.
It's one of her tricks!
Alpha Waymond:
Sir?
Our readings indicate it's not Jobu Tupaki.
...But if she's not here...
Oh shit
Do not engage!
Run!
Watch these two here
while I deal with Jobu!
I'm not risking the safety
of the Alpha Verse
for this.
[un-beep]
Alpha Waymond:
Get us as far away from Joy as you can
I'll be back. I promise.
No-no-no wait-
Joy: Hello?
Waymond: Joy?
Evelyn: No, no!
Waymond: Joy's here!
Evelyn: No, no no, that's not Joy!
Waymond: Joy!
Joy! I'm coming!
Okay! Be patient!
This is heavy!
Joy! Why are you here?
Joy: I have no fucking clue!
Waymond: Hey, gentle language!
Joy: Dude, what is going on?
Waymond: I'm sure there's a very
good explanation for all of this!
[scream]
Joy: What the fuck, mom?!
What the fuck are you doing?!
Evelyn: She's too powerful.
Joy: Are we all having a stroke?
Evelyn: You are like puppets.
You know? Puppets?
You can do things you normally cannot do.
It's like that movie!
Um.
That movie!
Joy: Okay, what are you talking about?
Evelyn: Raccoccoonie!
Waymond: What?
Joy: Huh?
Evelyn: Raccoccoonie!
Evelyn: You know, the one with the chef!
And he makes bad food. Phtooie!
And then!
This raccoon sit on his head
Control him!
And then he cooks good food!
Joy: Do you mean Ratatouille?
Waymond: Ratatouille? I like that movie!
Evelyn: No, no no no no no!
Raccoccoonie!
With the raccoon!
Everybody stop making up sounds!
Waymond: So there's-
there's a raccoon Joy
and a raccoon me
and they're controlling us?
Evelyn: Yeah, from the other universe
Waymond: That's very funny, Evelyn!
Evelyn: Okay, sounds little bit ridiculous
but
it's true!
I swear to god! You, you are macho man
Waymond: I like that!
Gong-gong: Evelyn
Evelyn
Waymond: Don't worry, dada
will get you out of this
Joy: Okay
Evelyn: Appa?
Alpha Gong-gong:
Quickly.
While she is distracted.
Evelyn: No!
Alpha Gong-gong:
It's only protocol.
It gives her one less universe to access!
Joy: Can you-
Waymond: Oh, it's Becky!
Hi Becky! Hold on-
Alpha Gong-gong
How do you expect to defeat her in every universe
if you can't even kill her in one?
Evelyn: She's your granddaughter!
Alpha Gong-gong:
How do you think I feel?
But it's a sacrifice that is necessary
to win the war
Waymond: Okay, there we go
Alpha Gong-gong:
You must do it.
Go.
Evelyn: Wh-
Joy: Yeah, my mom taped me to a chair
Because of...
raccoons
Waymond: Okay, be patient
Joy: Yeah, it's a long story, okay
Waymond: Daddy- daddy's trying
Joy: Mom?
Joy: Why are you--?
What are you doing?
Waymond: Hey! I almost had it!
Aw, come on!
Alpha Gong-gong:
You are already under her spell.
Joy: Holy shit. Holy shit! He has a gun!
Waymond: Everyone stay calm!
I think it's time for
a family discussion!
Evelyn: It's okay
It's okay
I won't let you kill her.
Alpha Gong-gong:
Don't you see what is happening to your mind?
In my universe
You pushed your
own daughter too hard
until you broke her
You!
You created Jobu Tupaki!
Joy: When did he get so good at English?
Alpha Gong-gong:
Now I must stop you
Otherwise-
It's only a matter of time
before you become...
just like her.
Evelyn: Just...
like...
her...
Waymond: Huh?
Alpha Gong-gong:
What the fuck are you do--
Waymond: Evelyn!
I don't think now is
a good time to dance!
[awkward beep]
Evelyn: Appa
I know you don't agree with me
But this is something I have to do!
Joy: What the f-
Waymond: That sounds weird!
Alpha Gong-gong:
No, no no no-
Wait, wait- you don't know
where you'll jump!
[awkward beep]
Warning! Unstable!
Please...
I cannot lose another loved one to the darkness...
Evelyn: Don't worry
You won't.
[awkward beep]
Man: Hey, uh
Clean up in there, alright?
Here- hoh!
Alpha Gong-gong:
Where did she jump?!
Evelyn: Sorry Appa!
Evelyn: Come on!
That way!
Oh no!
Come on!
Warning!
Mind fracturing!
Alpha Gong-gong:
Send every jumper
with a counterpart in the area!
Now!
One again
the Alpha Verse finds itself
as the last line of defense
against total chaos
Be brave. This Evelyn is as
stubborn as the others!
She has given us no choice
We must kill her before
she becomes another
Jobu Tupaki!
Evelyn: Joy!
Joy: Wh-what?
Joy.
I know
you have these
feelings
feelings that make you so sad
that makes you...
just want to give up
It's not your fault.
Not your fault.
I know...
It's- it's her.
Juju
Chewbacca
She...
has your soul
in the palm of her hand
Joy: What are you talking about.
Evelyn: The only way I can defeat her
To save you
Is to become like her.
Alpha Gong-gong:
Evelyn?
Your daughter is beyond saving!
And soon, you will be, too!
Your time is up!
Find your jumping pads!
[ladelling Ave Maria]
[business electrocution]
[sensual pylon licking]
[typical photocopying]
Waymond: I think you're pushing
things too far!
Evelyn: Or not far enough.
Waymond: Oh! Oh my god!
Oh my god!
Evelyn!
Joy: Oh my god.
What are you doing?
[beep]
Joy: Holy...
Shit.
Waymond: Is he dead?!
Evelyn: See? Not dead. Go!
Hurry up!
Come on, guys!
Joy: Dad, go!
Oh, my god!
Big-nose: Does my baby
wanna go for a walk?
My Toddy!
Joy: Orange soda...?
What is she doing?
Waymond: I- I think when
she does something weird
it helps her fight!
It gives her power!
Big-nose: Sorry baby.
[beep]
Big-nose: NO!
Toddy!
You...
Bitch!
Evelyn: Go!
Evelyn-
If you don't step up I'm giving some of your shifts to Chad
Chad: [chef wink]
Waymond: Huh? What happened?
Joy: I think they lost their...
Powers?
Man: Sir?
I'm gonna need another jumping pad.
[horrified realisation]
Waymond: I think she needs to
do something weird again!
Joy: What's he doing?
Waymond: I think she needs to
do something weird again!
Joy: Oh my god he's trying to
stick it in his butt.
Evelyn: NO!
Waymond: Uh, Evelyn!
Do jumping jacks!
Joy: That's not weird at all.
Waymond: Um
Joy: No, no no!
Slap him!
Joy: Mom, just
Blow on his nose!
Both: What?
It'll make him...
involuntarily scream
and do weird noises!
Waymond: Trust her, Evelyn!
It's really weird!
[ominous beep]
[counter-beep]
Waymond: Wow. Mom is really good!
Evelyn: Oh, sorry!
Reaching mental capacity.
Joy: Holy shit!
Alpha Gong-gong:
I'm sorry, Evelyn.
Mind fracturing
Alpha Gong-gong:
I'm sorry, Evelyn.
Mind fracturing
We'll die together.
[beep]
Pinky-
Go!
I see her-
[smash noise]
Waymond: Evelyn!
Evelyn!
No need to explain.
Alpha Waymond:
I have been watching you.
Evelyn: You're back!
Did you see how good I am?
I'm going to do it.
I am going to defeat that
Jobu Tupaki
Alpha Waymond:
Hey
You got her name right.
Evelyn
What you're doing is crazy!
Reckless
Your stupid plan to somehow
save your daughter
has managed to piss off
everyone
in the multiverse
And it just might work.
Evelyn: What?
[jobens the door]
Alpha Waymond:
I only wish I could be there
to see you finish this
Evelyn: What do you mean you
don't see me finish?
Alpha Waymond:
I'm grateful
that chance was kind enough
to let us have these last
few moments together
Alpha Waymond?
Waymond: What happened?
Was I raccoon Waymond again?
Evelyn: Raccoon Waymond is dead.
Waymond: And that's-- Raccoon Joy?
Am I getting it?
Evelyn: I'm gonna stop you, Jobu.
Now that I'm reaching my full potential.
Jobu Tupaki:
No, you still can't see what's happening.
Evelyn: No, I see clearly.
More clearly than ever before!
Waymond: Oh my god! Evelyn!
Oh my god!
Jobu Tupaki:
Damnit.
So close.
Waymond: Evelyn!
Evelyn?
Please help her!
Jobu Tupaki:
I'll see you again soon.
(singing) Somewhere out there...
(singing) In all that noise...
Waymond: Don't leave! Help her! Please!
Help!
HELP!
Evelyn: Where is she?
Where's our daughter?
Successful Waymond:
Daughter?
(singing) We're a family!
Raccoccoonie: Culinarily!
Chef Chad: Culinarily!
Both: Now we're cooking!
Chad: Oh
Raccoccoonie: Why nobody's lucky
Chad: Raccoccoonie
Chad: I don't know what I'd do without you.
Evelyn: Raccoccoonie?
Chad: Yeah, we make a pretty good team
Raccoccoonie: We're a family
Both: Culinarily
Raccoccoonie: Oh no
Chad: You can't tell no one
Raccoccoonie: She's seen too much!
Raccoccoonie: You know what that means.
Get her. Get her!
Chad: I'm begging you!
Evelyn: No, no, please, no, I-
Hot-dog Evelyn: What do you want?
Hot-dog Dierdre: I want... you.
Hot-dog Evelyn: No!
Stop that!
Stay back!
Hot-dog Dierdre: What, it's not wrong-
[sobs in condiment]
Actress Evelyn: I can think of
whatever nonsense I want
Evelyn: I did it.
Waymond: Don't forget these cookies!
Ms. Dierdre really likes it.
Waymond: Not yet, not yet!
Becky: Hiiii Mrs. Woooong
Joy: Hey mom, so about this morning-
Evelyn: Ohhh, enough with your tricks!
Joy: What?
Evelyn: I know you're in there!
Joy: Whoa!
Evelyn: Get out of my daughter!
Joy: Whoa-kay mom
Joy: are you already drunk?
Evelyn: Get out of my daughter!
Jobu: Hey Becky?
Becky: Mmhmm?
Jobu: Can you go help my
dad with the party?
Becky: Now?
Jobu: Yeah.
Evelyn: Go, go!
Jobu: Thanks, babe.
Jobu Tupaki:
You see it all, don't you?
You can see...
...how everything...
...is just a random rearrangement
of particles in a...
...vibrating superposition.
Evelyn: I have no idea what
you are talking about
but I can-
Huh?
Jobu Tupaki:
But you see
how everything
we feel
gets washed away
in a sea of every
other possibility
You're everywhere.
You're like me.
Evelyn: That's right.
I'm the one you're looking for.
I'm the one who's
going to defeat you!
Jobu Tupaki:
Hahaha, okay.
Hit me.
Punch my face.
Jobu: Oh!
Jobu: Ah!
Jobu: Ow!
Evelyn: Oh, stop.
Jobu: Woooow.
Jobu: Hi, dad.
Evelyn: We- we- we're just practicing
karaoke for tonight!
Jobu: La la la!
Evelyn: I will take care of it!
Jobu: She'll take care of it, dad.
Evelyn: Go!
Waymond: Honey, you okay?
Jobu: Yeah, I just fell
on the couch.
Evelyn: Go!
Waymond: Okay.
Jobu Tupaki:
So sweet.
[sighs]
Okay.
Jobu Tupaki: Hey!
Hey!
Evelyn: What, but
Buddy!
Evelyn: If you don't want to fight me
Th- wh- th- th- then-
Why?
Jobu Tupaki:
Why wha?
Evelyn: Wh- wh- what's all this for?
Jobu Tupaki:
Why was I looking for you?
Evelyn: Yeah.
Jobu Tupaki:
Siddown.
Siddooown!
Grab a snack!
Make yourself comfortable!
Yeah?
Oh
Hey
You okay?
Evelyn: Okay
Jobu Tupaki:
Mmph
We can speed this up.
Sit on the crack.
Sit on the crack of the couch.
Okay?
Get comfortable
[smiles in bagel]
Evelyn: Bagel...
Please!
I don't care about the bagel
I don't care about the Alpha Verse!
I only care about my Joy!
Give me back my daughter and
I'll leave you alone forever!
Jobu Tupaki:
Sorry!
No can do.
Evelyn: (whispers) Why not?!
Jobu Tupaki:
I am your daughter.
Your daughter is me.
Every version of Joy
is
Jobu Tupaki
You can't separate us.
Evelyn: N-no
Jobu Tupaki:
I have felt
everything your daughter has felt
and I know...
the joy
and the pain of having you
as my mother
Evelyn: Then you know
I would do--
only do the right thing for her
For you
Jobu Tupaki:
Right is a tiny box
invented by people
who are afraid
And I know what it feels like
to be trapped inside that box.
Joy: Mom...
Evelyn: No, it's not like that...
It's Gong-gong
He's a different generation!
Jobu Tupaki:
No, you don't have to
hide behind him anymore.
You should feel relieved
The Bagel
will show you the
true nature of things
You'll be free from that box
just like me.
Evelyn: No!
No.
I'm not like you.
You- you- you're young.
And life is always changing
I still know who I am.
Jobu Tupaki:
You have no idea what you've done.
You're stuck like this forever.
Evelyn: No
I'm going back with my Joy
to my family
to live my life
a happy life!
Jobu Tupaki:
Okay.
Good luck with that.
Waymond: Thank you so much
for coming!
Thank you, thank you!
Bye bye!
Jobu Tupaki:
All this time
I wasn't looking for you
so I could kill you
I was just looking for
someone who could
see what I see
feel
what I feel
Jobu Tupaki:
And that someone
Is you.
Waymond: Evelyn!
You're alive!
Alpha Gong-gong:
Impossible!
Evelyn: Hello?
Dierdre: Mrs. Wang?
Where-
Where are you?
I mean, to not even show up?
For your appointment?
Evelyn: Shut up.
Dierdre: What did you just say?
Evelyn: I said shut up.
You don't matter
Hot-dog Diedre:
Whatever I did, I'm sorry...
Evelyn: Nothing matters.
Dierdre:
Mrs. Wang!
You are going to be in serious trouble!
[bagel distortions]
Do you understand?
Now you can disrespect--
[beep]
Evelyn: Happy new year!
Another year, hmm?
Pretending we know what
we're doing, but really?
We're just going around
in circles
Doing laundry
taxes
and laundry
and taxes
No more running.
Dierdre: Excuse me,
where are the owners?
Oh!
There you are
Mr. and Mrs. Wang
You have left me no option
but to authorise
the seizure of your personal
and your business assets
You have to vacate the premises
Chad: What are you doing-
No! No!
What the--
Raccoccoonie: Chad I told you she
couldn't be trusted!
Waymond: Evelyn!
Please!
Calm down!
Dierdre: Within 48 hours, or--
Evelyn: Ev...ry...thing...
Waymond: What are you doing?
Not a single moment will go by
without every other universe
screaming for your attention
Never fully there...
just a lifetime of...
Chad: No, master, no!
Jobu: Fractured moments...
Chad: Raccoccoonie!!
Contradictions and confusion...
Chad: Get off me!
Raccoccoonie: Chad, don't forget about me
Chef: Get off me!
Diedre: Here are the papers.
Oh!
Who-o-oa! Officer!
Jobu Tupaki:
With only a few specks of time
where anything actually makes any sense
Evelyn: I've always hated this place...
Waymond: Evelyn!
Chad: Raccoccoonie!
Raccoccoonie: Chaaaad!
Jobu Tupaki:
You know why I actually built the bagel?
It wasn't do "destroy everything"...
It was to destroy myself.
I wanted to see if I went in
could I finally escape
Like, actually die?
At least this way...
I don't have to do it alone.
Diedre: Um, excuse me
excuse me, Mr. Wang
every person I know is going
through a hard time
it's a hard time
Jobu: Evelyn
Come back
Evelyn: My silly husband...
Probably making things worse
Jobu Tupaki:
Ignore it.
[Diedre sighs]
Diedre: Okay, you can let her go.
You--
Let her go.
It's okay.
Yes!
Thank you.
Evelyn: How?
That's impossible
Jobu: It's just a
statistical inevitability
That's impossible
Jobu: It's just a
statistical inevitability
It's nothing special.
Waymond: I don't know
I just talked to her.
Waymond: Please!
Please!
Can we--
Can we just stop fighting?
I know you're all
fighting because you're scared
and confused
I'm confused, too!
All day
I don't know what
the heck is going on
But...
Somehow...
This feels like it's all my fault
I don't know
The only thing I do know
is that we have to be kind
Please
Be kind?
Especially when we don't
know what's going on
Jobu: Hey, Evelyn!
Bagel?
Alpha Gong-gong:
Evelyn...
Jobu Tupaki:
You can still turn around
and avoid all this
Waymond: Please
Be kind
Evelyn: It's too late, Waymond
Waymond: Don't say that
Did you see that?
What song is this?
Thanks!
Thank you for coming!
That's very funny!
Yeah! That's it! Yeah!
I'm sorry...
Jobu Tupaki:
Ooooh!
So cute!
C'mon, Evelyn.
Come on.
Oh.
I get it.
Feelin' a good thing.
They got your hopes up.
See, I'm here to save
you some time.
Eventually?
That all just goes away.
Now come on.
I don't care if you come with me!
Enjoy your life.
Waymond: Evelyn!
Evelyn!
Please!
No more!
Evelyn: I don't want to hurt you
Joy, come back with me!
Joy!
What did my
silly husband say to you?
Diedre: He told me
about your situation
I remembered when my husband...
...served me papers
I drove his Kia Forte
through my neighbour's kitchen
Evelyn: Huh
Diedre: You know what I say?
It's cold, and unlovable
bitches like us
that make the world go round
Hot-dog Evelyn:
Don't stop playing
Play something for me?
[plays Clair de Lune]
Evelyn: That's not true
You're not unloveable
Diedre: What are you
talking about?
Evelyn: There is always
something to love!
Even in a stupid, stupid universe
where we have hot-dogs
for fingers
We get very good
with our feet!
Diedre: Okay
I feel nothing
I f-
I feel...
I...
(sobbing) f-feel
Alpha Gong-gong:
Don't let her stop Jobu!
Open fire!
So stupid!
Waymond: Evelyn...
What are you doing?
Evelyn: I'm learning
to fight
like you.
Man: You know, Evelyn
My wife used to wear that exact same
perfume, god rest her soul?
Evelyn: These are
direct indications that
there is impingement
on the nervous system
With a little bit of help
we should be seeing things
go nice and straight
[healing necksnap]
You might feel a little sore
but everything is
looking pretty good
Man: Thank you
Man: Clean up in there, alright?
Chad: You took everything
away from me
Evelyn: I'm sorry
Chad: Raccoccoonie taught
me so much!
I-
I didn't even know
How to boil an egg!
He taught me how to
spin it on
a spatula!
Raccoccoonie: Chaaaad!
I'm useless alone
Evelyn: We're all useless, alone
It's a good thing
you're not alone
Let's go rescue your silly raccoon
Alpha Gong-gong:
Get out of the way!
Evelyn: Waymond!
Jobu Tupaki:
See?
It's only a matter of time
before everything
balances itself back
Evelyn: Come on, come on, go!
before everything
balances itself back
Chad: I can't!
I'm sorry, Raccoccoonie!
Raccocoonie: Chaaad!
I'm sorry...
Alpha Gong-gong:
Evelyn
Let her go.
Evelyn: But she turned out
to be stubborn
Aimless
A mess
Just like her mother.
But now I see
it's okay that she's a mess
because just like me
Jobu Tupaki:
Well, maybe you win in this universe
But in another?
I...
beat...
you!
Or...
we...
tie!
Or we just...
hang around.
Evelyn: Okay, Joy
Listen--
Jobu: 'Cause it's
all just a pointless
swirling bucket of bullshit!
That bagel is where we
finally find peace, Evelyn
Evelyn: Stop calling me
Evelyn!
I...
am...
your...
mother!
Apa?
Jobu: Seriously?!
Can you please
just
STOP!
Mom!
just-
Just stop!
Well good for you
you're figuring your shit out
That's
great. I'm really
really
happy for you.
But I-
I'm tired
I don't wanna hurt anymore and
for some reason when
I'm with you it just-
it just hurts the both of us.
So let's just go our separate ways, okay?
Just let me
go
Evelyn: Okay.
Wait.
You are getting fat.
And you never call me
even though we have family plan.
Joy: What.
Evelyn: And it's free!
You only visit
when you need something!
And you got a tattoo!
And I don't care
if it's supposed to
represent our family
you know I hate tattoos
And-
of all the places I could be?
Why would I want
to be here with you?
Yes.
You're right.
It doesn't make sense!
Waymond: Evelyn
Joy: Let her finish!
Evelyn: Maybe it's like you said
Maybe there is something out there
Some new discovery
that will make us feel
like even smaller pieces of shit
Something that explains why
you still went looking for me
through all of this noise
and why
no matter what
I still want to be here with you
I will always
Always
want to be here with you.
Joy: So what?
Are you just gonna
ignore everything else?
You could be anything, anywhere
Why not go somewhere where your
where your daughter is more than just
this?
Here, all we get
are a few
specks of time where
any of this actually makes any sense
Evelyn: Then I will cherish
these few specks of time
Dierdre: Push the button
There
Down you go
I feel like I'm fourteen...
[laughs] Yeah
Chad: I'm sorry, Raccoccoonie
I'm sor...
What are you doing?
Evelyn: Grab my hair!
Becky: What did he say?
Joy: So awkward...
It's awkward, right?
...Do you still wanna do your party?
Evelyn: We could do whatever we want.
Nothing matters.
Joy: Okay, we're definitely late now, guys.
Do you have to bring all of these?
Evelyn: Mmhm
That needs to go in the back, too.
Joy: Taxes suck.
Waymond: Thank you
for the ride, Becky!
Joy: Hey
Things okay?
Becky: Mmhm. You got this, okay?
Evelyn: Becky?
Joy: I'll call you after
Evelyn: You need to
grow your hair
Joy: I'll call you later!
I gotta pee.
Hold on.
Evelyn: Okay
Diedre: Okay.
Yes.
I am happy to say
I do think...
Things are better.
This is
This is, uh, an improvement
And I'm-
I'm glad that you listened.
But! We have a problem
Because you listened,
but you didn't listen
And that has to do with the
Schedule Cs
You see--
Evelyn!
Did you hear me?
Evelyn: Sorry
What did you say?
Subtitles by Salrith